(Igawa) Now (Tsumura) Masaki Igawa and Mayumi Igawa are
Their memories have been tampered with
I was living as a different person.
Her real name is Nanami Ishino
He's the murderer who killed my husband.
(Mayumi) I didn't kill you.
When did you get your memory back?
(Mayumi) I started getting a headache.
Memories from before started coming to mind
Probably a drug manufacturer called Neurovise is involved.
(Mayumi) There was one woman I didn't know.
Mutsumi Kosaka, my old boss.
You are in most of my happy memories
Even though it's all a lie
(Yuri) Our old photos
Kento and the three...
I would do anything if I could go back to that time again.
come back
(Tsujimoto) These are the people Kosaka-san was in charge of.
All of them were sentenced to life imprisonment for murder.
All nine people here have disappeared from prison.
The plan is to rewrite criminals' memories and reintegrate them into society.
Is Ninomiya among these? There was no record of an arrest.
Talk to Kosaka-san...
(car running sound)
📱(conflict sound)
♬〜
(Kousaka)《This is...》 (Uemoto)《What do you think? 》
(Kousaka)《Is this possible? 》
《Rewriting memories...》
《Our company originally had PTSD and
To create a drug to treat dementia
I have been conducting various research
In addition to erasing memories
I succeeded in planting a new one.
《Memories are converted into electronic symbols from the brain of the donor body.
You can freely design your memories based on that.
Now I can do it.
《Such a thing...》
(Kamimoto)《The Persona Shift program is
using that technology
A prisoner sentenced to life imprisonment
Return to society as a different person
This is a project where you can contribute.
《We would like to ask for your cooperation as we will soon enter the testing phase》
《Already at the testing stage...》
《That shouldn't be allowed.》
《Director Sakita has also approved》
(Kamimoto)《What's the problem? 》
"This is a clear violation of human rights. Rewriting memories..."
(Kamimoto)《Then, the prisoners will be financed by the people's tax money until they die.
Are you saying it's better to let them eat? 》
《Hahaha…》
(Uemoto)《You've seen it a lot》
《Scum who are not willing to be rehabilitated》
(Uemoto)《Those who show no signs of remorse and have no room for rehabilitation.
It's society's trash.
《This project has selected such garbage.
Isn't it great to reuse?
♬〜
《I'll pretend I didn't ask you anything. Excuse me.》
《Now that you know, please cooperate.》
``Thank you for bringing you this far.''
I thought you'd give it back.
♬〜
(Kousaka) ≪This shouldn't happen.
I was thinking≫
(Kousaka) ≪Until that day...≫
(Male)《Ah... Ugh...》
(Female)《Kya! 》
(Murotani)《Urusaeena》
(High school student)《Ugh...》
"(scream)"
(Detective)《Once we arrive, we will check the damage situation》 (Detective)《Yes! 》
《(Vibration sound of mobile phone)》
"(scream)"
♬〜
《Tsujimoto hold it! " "yes! 》
(Murotani)《Hahahaha, it's your fault that I failed to kill him.
There must be someone suffering.
《I'll make things easier for you right now, so let go of me》
《Ah...》 (Tsujimoto)《Mr. Tsumura! 》
《Shit...》 (Murotani)《Hey! 》
《Hey, I've memorized your face, so be prepared if it shows up.》
``Don't think you'll ever see sunlight again.''
"You're going to die inside the fence! 》
(Tsujimoto)《Mr. Tsumura! 》 《Let go! 》
(Tsujimoto)《Please calm down! Mr. Tsumura》
《The main defendant is sentenced to life imprisonment》
♬〜
(Uemoto)《Yeah》
(Prison Officer) I'm Takatoshi Muroya, please.
♬〜
(Kousaka) “Takatoshi Muroya, the first subject of the Persona Shift program…”
《Let's take a break once we're done here》
"yes! 》
(Kousaka) “Returning to Muroya and returning to society as Naoya Tachibana”
"Neurovis personnel will be monitoring him."
(Staff)《Tachibana, have you had your company's regular checkup? 》
《Ah, no, not this month yet》
《It's free, so take it.》
《I'll make a reservation》
"thank you! 》
(Kousaka) “Does your memory as Naoya Tachibana stick?
I check it regularly and there are no problems so far."
"good morning! good morning! 》
(Kousaka)《No abnormalities were observed in either work attitude or daily life.
It's like a different person》
《Because I'm a different person hehehehe...》
《Next test subject candidate》 (Uemoto) 《Yes》
(Tatsuya)《You're in the way, get out of the way》
(Murotani)《I'm sorry》《Don't be dirty! What are you doing! 》
(Staff) 《We are very sorry! 》
《Aaah, I'm so noisy now》
(Female)《Kya! 》
《Noisy》
``Don't think you'll ever see sunlight again.''
"You're going to die inside the fence! 》
♬〜
(Tatsuya)《Ugh…》 (Murotani)《Yo》
《Ugh! 》
《Ugh... Wow...》
♬〜
《Do it》 (Tatsuya) 《Huh! 》
《Ugh... ugh...》
《Ugh! 》
♬〜
《Achii》
《Kousaka-san! 》
《Mr. Tsumura...》
♬〜
(Kousaka) ≪What I was afraid of has happened≫
(Kousaka)《Muroya regains his memory
After killing Tatsuya Ishino, who was in trouble.
It seems that he also set out to take revenge on Tsumura》
《It seems like my life was saved.
As soon as I regain consciousness, I will hear from Murotani.
《There's no need for that.》 《What? 》
《Murotani is assumed to be dead》
《Murotani escaped from prison.
He headed towards Tsumura and was attacked.
《Wait a minute, then Tsumura is the murderer...》
(Kamimoto)《Unavoidable》
``The existence of the project must not be known.''
(Kamimoto)《Muroya will be transferred to the facility that Neurovis used in the past》
《What happened to his brain there?
Let's investigate thoroughly》
《This project is here
I can't let it end, you know? 》
♬〜
(Kousaka)《It looks like she will get married and have children》
《I see. Good.》
《When I leave here...》
《You should move on with your life》
"yes"
《That... is the best compensation》
♬〜
《Please proceed》
《Trial and error is important in everything》
《Don't worry about your subordinates》
"yes"
♬〜
(Staff)《Hey, did you go for a checkup? 》
《Yes, I went, thank you》
♬〜
(Kousaka)《Yes》
《What? 》
``Isn't it going back? 》
♬〜
(Kousaka) ≪Why are humans the only ones?
I guess I learned to regret it≫
(Kousaka) 《Yusuke Ninomiya passed away》 《What? 》
《He was hit by a truck and died instantly》
《Like that...》
♬〜
《Have you ever heard the name Masaki Igawa? 》
"Yichuan?" 》
《While I was there, I also talked to a reporter I knew.
I had him watch Ninomiya and the others.》
《The reporter recently
I found someone who looks just like Ninomiya》
《Isn't it similar to someone else? 》
《Your friend passed away two years ago》
《Better forget about it》
(Kousaka) ≪I would do anything if I could be forgotten≫
``What happened? 》
《Right after Ninomiya saw me
I held my head and crouched down, trying to hide my face.
《Head? Did you talk to him? 》
《I ran away right after that.》
(Kousaka) ≪If you could turn back time, what would it be...≫
(conflict sound)
Ugh... ah...
ah…
Tsujimoto… Tsujimoto!
Ah... ah...
(Ring tone)
Tsumura-san... go...
Ah... that's good...
Um... what happened?
A car crashed into me... I don't remember it at all.
It must have been because he hit his head. There was nothing wrong with his brain, so don't worry.
What about Tsumura-san? OK?
ah
(Tsujimoto) What car hit you? It's a stolen car
Did the person on board escape?
ah
It's not just a hit and run...
They were targeting us...
Maybe it's Kosaka-san?
♬〜
It was my fault for getting involved, wasn't it?
Are you this far?
I'll take care of the rest. Don't go any deeper.
No, wait...
♬〜
(typing sound)
Ah... I couldn't sleep so I went for a walk.
yes…
Were we being used as test subjects for something?
I don't care what happens to me because I'm a criminal.
Eh... that's it...
Actually, I haven't done it.
Don't you believe it?
I believe it
thank you
(Mayumi) What did you do? Huh?
Still can't remember anything?
Yeah…
If you can't remember, maybe it's okay to leave it as is.
It's quite difficult
♬〜
Let's go get it back
Huh?
Your daughter and your life too.
how?
I'm sure they want to shut your mouth
On the contrary, use it
maybe we can negotiate
♬〜
Haven't you found those two yet?
If I find it, I'll let you know right away.
Tada-san yes
(Aina) There's a customer in the consultation room... Ah, thank you.
Good job
Igawa-san, are you closed today as well?
Ah, it seems like your mother has collapsed.
It's hard to be with him all the time, isn't it?
(Tada) Hello, are you here to discuss moving in?
Thank you for your support.
You know Kosaka-san, right?
Mr. Kosaka? I don't quite remember it.
The residents here seem to be all dementia patients.
(Tada) No, well...
Operated by Neurovis Corporation
Um, sorry, I'm just a staff member.
I mean, it's almost like a part-time job.
I don't know. I'm sorry, but you're also a member of Neurovis.
I heard it from Kosaka-san.
Why did Mr. Kosaka choose you?
What is it? Are you pretending to be a great detective?
After all, it was connected to Kosaka-san.
I don't know anything! haven't said anything yet
Neurovis is
Developed drugs to treat PTSD and dementia
During that time, he created a technology to tamper with memory.
What is it? that
If there was something like that, I would like to do it too.
When I was in middle school, girls hated me so much that I couldn't believe it.
I want to erase the memory of that time.
♬〜
You know these nine people, right?
No... they are criminals
But why is there no one in prison right now?
Memories are tampered with by Neurovis
I don't know anything because I live as a different person.
Yusuke Ninomiya also had his memory manipulated.
But Ninomiya has no record of committing any crime.
Why did he have his memory messed with?
So you're saying I don't know anything!
Come back! Please come back!
Then I'll go home!
♬〜
(Tada) Mr. Kosaka's former subordinate is aware of it.
Regarding the PS program... What should I do?
Will you capture me and erase my memory?
Wait a minute
♬〜
I just want to talk
(Staff) Welcome.
It's safer to be in a place where there are people, right?
There is a private room on the second floor where you can talk quietly.
(Staff) Welcome.
(Staff) Please take your time.
Please come anytime
What did you do to me and Mr. Ninomiya?
I saw you right before your memory was messed with
Were you the one who accused me of killing my husband?
Answer!
it is…
I don't think I'm sorry
But I had no choice
Eh...
You can't agree with that, can you?
7 years? 7 years I was separated from my daughter.
Do you know how painful that is?
Yeah (Mayumi) There's no way I can understand!
You see your daughter every day, right?
I haven't been able to see my daughter for a while due to something happening.
♬〜
pretend I didn't see anything
pretend I didn't hear anything
instead, set me free
Let me live with Miu
♬〜
I understand how you feel.
But I'm sorry
What does it mean?
Miu…
♬〜
why…
(Mayumi) Why...
♬〜
(notification sound)
Yes📱Mr. Tsumura, this is Ikawa.
Mayumi was taken away?
♬〜
Sorry
This is Mayumi's GPS.
I was giving it to you in case something happened.
♬〜
In this?
(sound of water flowing)
Have you worked together with Kosaka-san for a long time?
Ah, that's why I can't forgive
I'll stop you before you make any more mistakes.
What? here
♬〜
Here...
What are you doing here?
It's you
What do you plan to do with Nanami Ishino?
You brought her here two years ago, right?
This is information about the nine people who disappeared from prison, including Muroya.
I noticed this when I saw this
Eight of the nine were sentenced to life imprisonment.
Only Nanami Ishino received a 10 year sentence.
There must have been other people sentenced to life imprisonment.
why was she chosen
What do you mean?
She didn't kill her husband, she did...
Isn't it Muroya?
The test subject of a project that was being carried out in secret
There's no way you could announce that you killed an ordinary person.
So the wife decided to kill her husband.
You and Neurovice teamed up to do this.
That's not all
He tried to kill me and Tsujimoto when he found out about the project.
♬〜
Don't you deny it?
Please do it!
How many people have died because of you?
Do you think your life has been ruined?
I thought this project had a future.
If I rewrite my memory
What if I could live forever as a different person?
how good is it
Don't you think so?
(Kousaka) Forget everything, even now and this moment.
can live another happy life
Are criminals the guinea pigs?
Yeah
Why did you mess with Ninomiya's memory?
Even pretending that Ninomiya was dead
Why did you choose to be reborn as Masaki Igawa?
What did Ninomiya do?
Everything
Ah...
♬〜
(Ring tone)
(cell phone vibration sound)
Welcome back Ninomiya
📱"Please leave a message after the tone"
Ah, Mr. Tsumura, this is Tsujimoto.
I was just checking the security cameras near the scene of the hit-and-run.
Near the scene...
(Tsujimoto) Yusuke Ninomiya was there.
♬〜
``When did your memory return? 》
《If you follow your subordinates,
I saw you crawling out of the car that crashed into Tsumura and the others.
``Why did you do that? 》
``Because Tsumura tried to close in on us.
Did you try to erase it? 》
♬〜
《Please do not touch Yuri or Kento》
《I will cooperate with you》
《They definitely want to shut your mouth.》
《On the other hand, you might be able to use that to negotiate.》
《Nanami Ishino will come to you》
《I have an idea...》
♬〜
《Use this》
《Mr. Tsumura, this is Ikawa》
《Mayumi was taken away》
♬〜
Please keep your promise
Yeah
(chime)
Welcome back...
♬〜
Mr. Igawa?
Welcome back...
Yuri
Eh...
I'm home
Yusuke?
(sound of door closing)
I'm home
♬〜
Welcome back
《Well, let's say I mess with this guy's memory...》
《Is Nanami Ishino okay? 》
《Somehow I couldn't erase my memory》
《I will try rewriting my memory from scratch instead of just a part of it》
《I will be ready by tomorrow》
《Yeah, then I'll keep you locked up here until then.》
♬〜
《(locking sound)》
《Everything is back to normal...》
♬〜
Are you okay now?
The police are on the move, so there's no need to worry anymore.
What about Tsumura-san?
He was... caught.
After all, he was killing people.
Like that...
Because he won't appear in front of us anymore
Now everything... everything is back to normal.
♬〜
(sound of door opening)
Kento welcome back
Welcome back Kento
♬〜
♬(pianica)
That's amazing. I practiced a lot with Kento (Sage).
Did you practice a lot? I was good at it because
Shall we do it again? Okay, do it again.
♬〜
Ah... ah...
Shit...
Ninomiya!
Shit... open it! Ninomiya!
Damn... Ninomiya!
(sound of knocking on the door)
Open it!
Ninomiya!
♬〜
You remember everything, right?
It's okay now
Ninomiya was a Neurovis person.
2 years ago Why did you rewrite your memories?
If you don't do well, the police might be involved.
They kidnapped a wise man...
forget it
To smile in front of your loved ones